NO ANIMALS WERE HARMED DURING
THE FILMING OF THIS PRODUCTION
A message has just arrived from
the castle, my Bey.
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com
''If you don't give Kulacahisar back...
... I will sentence Bayhoca to death.''
Lena!
No. Please, no!
Bayhoca.
My Bayhoca.
If I return without my nephew...
... my horse and my beyhood robe...
... shall become my coffin.
If I...
... don't fulfill my promise...
... the Tent of Ertuğrul Gazi...
... shall be my graveyard.
Careful! Ambush!
BEFORE
Where are you taking me?
Didn't anyone tell you that curiosity is a
bad thing?
You should kill me while you can.
I don't agree with you, young man.
Your life is not enough. I want all
the Kayı Tent to beg for their lives.
You have no idea about your enemy, Nikola.
Only for Allah, a Kayı Alp falls on his
knees.
You've started to talk non sense.
Did you already get accustomed to beating?
Send my regards to the Lord of
İznik, Alexander.
I hope he likes my little present over
here.
I'm sure he will, Nikola.
And you'll be rewarded too.
This is the aim of my life.
Pleasing your friends.
Alexander, be careful.
I don't want to see you at the hands of
Turks again.
If I ever come across them, I will bring
the head of their Bey, Osman, to you.
If you meet my Bey again, know that your
head will leave your body.
Shut his mouth and mount him on the horse.
Just like his uncle, he talks non sense.
On your horses, soldiers!
A message from our spy in İnegöl, my Bey.
We know what Nikola is about to do.
He is going to send Bayhoca to the
Lord of İznik.
Lord of İznik?
What about sentencing him to death?
He came up with a better plan I guess.
It might be a trap.
Ever since I came to this tent, our spy
has always been loyal to us.
Why should he lie now?
Come on. We must hurry up.
We have to save my son from those
heathens.
Osman.
Brother?
What happened to my anxious Osman?
What happened to my roaring brother?
What are we waiting for?
We can't lose more time.
Let's save my child.
Your nephew.
Let's go!
Allahu Akbar!
Please, have mercy.
We are just slaves.
Alps!
-Check the carriages!
-I'm here, son.
The carriages!
Brother.
Brother?
Alps!
Attack!
Feudal Landlord Nikola!
I came here to congratulate your
intellect.
Tell me, Helen!
Osman took the bait you threw at him.
Perfect!
Today I learned Aniton and his daughter
were the ones who helped Osman flee.
Let's tell him to cook for us.
And her daughter shall serve wine so
that I can kill them together.
Osman.
Brother!
Take my brother away!
Careful!
Ya Allah!
Draw your swords!
Alps!
Fall back!
Damn it! Don't let him run away!
Osman!
Let's go!
You won't escape from me this time!
Ya Allah!
This...
... is for my brother.
Brother.
Brother!
I'm okay.
He is okay and he will get better,
insallah.
Osman!
I'm going to finish you, Osman!
One day I'm going to catch you and
finish you off!
Alps! We are going to Tent.
-Come on!
-As you order, my Bey.
Brother.
Aniton.
Where is your daughter, Eftelya?
Where is Eftelya?
So you don't understand?
I'm going to kill you and your daughter,
Aniton.
Traitor dog!
You dog!
Your daughter is going to die
just like you.
Traitor!
They know everything.
This is your last chance.
You little devil.
You will no longer play tricks on us.
If there is something better than
killing a Turk...
... I'm pretty sure it must be killing
a traitor.
I'm going to kill you!
Don't worry.
You are next.
Take him.
Move!
Hold on, brother. Hold on.
Faster!
We are almost there.
To the Tent of healing!
Open the way!
Savcı!
Come on, faster!
Move aside!
Please, be strong.
Stop!
My Savcı.
Savcı!
My Savcı! Who did this to you?
Who could do such a thing to you?
Please say something!
I'm begging you, please!
We need to check his wound.
Open your eyes, Savcı!
-Aunt.
-Take your hands off me!
Where is my son, Osman Bey?
You made a promise! Where is he?
Not only my son but also my bey, you took
from me.
Shame on you.
Shame on you!
Open your eyes, Savcı!
Please, I'm begging you. Open your
eyes!
Savcı!
Come on!
Eftelya has just died too, Nikola.
Do you hear, young man? Someone else
died because of you again.
I'm going to drown you in your own blood.
What a pity.
His father said the same thing.
What happened to him?
What happened?
Do you want to know?
Flatyos stabbed him in the guts just
like this.
A hard death he will go through
I suppose.
You are lying!
Flatyos, can you please tell us what we
accomplished thanks to this young man?
We caught all the spies in our castle
thanks to him, Nikola.
Yes. What else?
And in exchange of his live, we will
get Kulacahisar back.
Do you hear?
Do you think my uncle Osman will leave
you unpunished?
Enough about your uncle already!
Man up a little bit.
Whatever had happened, happened
because of you!
The son of Ertuğrul Gazi, Savcı Bey, died
because of his stupid son!
You are lying.
Prepare to...
You will regret not killing me
already.
Stand him up.
Are you going to be my killer?
Listen to me carefully, young man.
Your uncle, Osman...
... in exchange of your life, he is going
to give back Kulacahisar...
... willingly and without having
second thoughts, to me.
-No!
-Yes!
Take him away.
Father!
-Please don't leave me, Savcı!
-Lena, step back!
Lena!
Please open your eyes, Savcı!
-Lena, stop.
-Here it is, Bala Hatun.
Don't touch me!
Get off!
Oh, Osman Bey!
Osman Bey! Oh, Osman Bey!
Your brother! Your brother!
How will you build your state
over your brother's body?
Enough, my girl!
Get off!
Come on! Come on!
How will you sit on that throne,
Osman Bey?
Hold on, my lion.
Hold on.
How will you sit on that throne,
Osman Bey?
Hold on, my lion.
Hurry, girls!
What are you waiting for?
Come on!
Give it to me.
Here it is.
Hold on, brother.
Hold on.
His wounds are heavy.
We should fire it.
Boil some water, women!
Hold on, my lion. Hold on!
He has a fever!
Hurry, I say! Hurry!
Prepare the ember!
Bring it!
Get off! Get off! Bring that here!
He will be healed!
I won't leave you!
Boil some water!
Don't let yourself go!
Brother...
Now, everyone saw that
Osman lost.
The rest will be easier.
Everyone loses, woman.
But a bey with many enemies
shouldn't lose.
Then, he'll be crushed under
his tent.
-Salam Alaikum.
-Alaikum Salam.
Nikola played us through our
spies in the castle.
He hit us on our hearts.
I wish...
...I hadn't listened to my brother.
I felt it.
His pain for his child,
made me weak.
In such times, instead of the enemy...
...your love hurt you.
We'll get over this as well.
With Allah's will, we'll get up.
Bayhoca.
No...
My bey, we found this.
If you don't leave Kulucahisar
tomorrow...
...like your spies...
...the owner of this armor will die.
Gather the beys at once.
Bayhoca or Kulucahisar.
Now is the time to decide.
Shame on you, Osman Bey.
You lost my son to the enemy.
And you used my husband as a bait.
Shame on you.
Your pain will end soon.
But the pain in my heart.
The pain in your heart.
-Be patient, Savcı.
-Lena.
Hazal Hatun, you see that I'm busy.
Leave.
I wouldn't come here if...
...the news didn't concern you.
Osman Bey's spy in Kulucahisar is
killed.
And Bayhoca...
How can I say...
Speak!
That heathen Nikola!
He sent Bayhoca's armor...
...and says that he will kill him
if we don't leave Kurucahisar.
No... No...
No...
My son... Please, my son...
Savcı... Please, my son...
No... No...
No...
My son... No...
With Allah's ninety-nine names...
...who creates everything and
fills our hearts with faith.
You all know the matter.
The heathen Nikola wants
Kulucahisar Castle...
...in return for my nephew Bayhoca.
I want to talk to you before
making the decision.
Bamsı Bey.
Kulucahisar Castle was conquered
with the price...
...of many lives and blood
from our martyrs.
I swore with my alps
in that castle...
...to never leave that castle
without a fight.
Now, I can't tell those lions...
...that we'll leave without a fight.
I won't.
So, Osman Bey...
...I don't want to leave
the castle.
-Brother.
-He is my nephew...
...but it's about a Kayı bey
rather than a nephew.
It hurts to leave him to the heathens,
I know.
We can't do anything, I know that too.
I'll give up on my life to save him.
But, Osman Bey, you know it too...
...our lands are sacred.
They can't be left for anyone's
favor.
What do you say, uncle?
-What do you say?
-Bayhoca...
...is like my grandson.
But even for him...
...we can't leave the castle.
We shouldn't even think about that.
The bey has Allah's blessing.
He has the wisdom.
He makes the best decision.
I'm sure that he'll make the right
decision.
A castle can be retaken.
But we can't revive a life lost.
We can't leave Bayhoca to the heathen.
We should leave the castle.
And get Bayhoca.
And this way...
...the war will be over.
We will...
...leave Kulucahisar.
Forgive me, Savcı.
I loved you at first sight.
I will love you until my
last breath.
If it's time for separation,
it doesn't fit us to rebel, you said.
But a mother's heart can't
take it.
I'm going to our son, Savcı.
If they try to kill our child...
...I want to protect him.
I want to see his eyes
for the last time.
That's all I can.
I know how much you care
about your honor.
Don't worry, I rather kill myself
than harm your honor.
Savcı...
...my valiant, give me your blessing.
Castles can get conquered.
Enemies can get defeated.
Lost provinces can get retaken.
But it's not easy to raise
a Kayı bey.
A Kayı bey can't be left
to the enemy.
For this reason, I'll get my
nephew back...
...and leave the castle.
That's my decision.
Osman Bey, am I hearing wrong?
Or are you leaving Kulucahisar?
You heard it right, Bamsı Bey.
I'm leaving Kulucahisar.
No, no. Osman Bey I know...
...Osman Bey I know can't say that.
-He wouldn't say that.
-You don't know me well then, Bamsı Bey.
Uncle. Go to the heathen Nikola.
Tell him that we are leaving the castle.
May I enter?
My bey.
Come, Baysungur.
Lena?
-Where is Lena?
-I don't know, my bey.
I haven't seen her.
I brought you ointment.
Lena?
Lena, no... No...
You can't go to that castle.
Baysungur!
Help me.
Help me. I need to talk to Osman.
I need to see Osman Bey.
Osman Bey!
Leaving a conquered castle is against
our traditions.
Even the bey can't step over the
traditions.
On this matter, Osman Bey,
I warn you.
The decision is made. There is no
reason to talk any longer.
It's my decision.
You wouldn't go against the traditions
if it wasn't your nephew.
You are right, Bamsı Bey.
He is my nephew.
And I want him here,
safe and sound.
Osman Bey!
I didn't live this long to see our
traditions disrespected!
If you will step over it,
you must step over me first!
Osman Bey.
Bamsı Bey.
What are you saying?
The future of Kayı...
...doesn't depend on that decision
or this attitude. Calm down.
We've talked and said everything.
Now, we'll get Bayhoca and
leave Kulucahisar.
This is my decision.
Osman Bey...
Osman Bey!
Lena went to the castle, brother.
Brother!
Don't worry.
I will save both Bayhoca
and Lena.
Come on, Baysungur.
Take my brother to his tent.
Everyone except Bamsı Bey will
leave.
Lena.
I've waited for you to come
for years.
But you came for your son.
Flatyos, is my son all right?
-Where is Bayhoca?
-If you hadn't married that Turk...
...he would be our son.
Flatyos...
...show me my son, let me see
that he is all right. I ask nothing else.
For the woman who chooses a Turk
over me...
...why should I do such a thing, Lena?
I'll beg you if you like.
I'll kneel befor you.
There is nothing I can't do for my child.
For Jesus Christ's sake, Flatyos.
Let me see my child.
Please.
Oh, brother, oh.
I thought wrong.
You are leaving the castle
for my child.
You faced us all to conquer
that castle.
Now you are facing everyone to
leave it. How can I repay you?
You have my blessing, brother.
But how can a conquered castle
be left?
It's against our traditions.
Don't.
Even for my child, don't.
You'll lose your power,
your supporters.
Don't.
My dear brother,
my dearest brother.
As long as you support me...
...I don't need anyone else.
Thank you, brother.
I'm wounded. You know, I can't do
anything. We've brought you trouble.
You weren't conscious, brother.
How could you know?
Don't worry, I'll save them both.
Whatever the price.
Brother...
...the castle...
Brother?
-Mother?
-Bayhoca!
What are you doing here?
Have they captured you?
What have they done to you?
Are you hurt?
No...
My child, how could they hurt you...
Mother? Are you not a captive?
What are you doing here?
My father?
How is my father?
-This is enough, Lena.
-Mother, do you know this dog?
Why is he treating you well?
My son...
Bayhoca...
I'll save you from here.
Don't worry.
This is enough.
Soldiers.
Flatyos, a little more, please.
Lena.
Where are you taking my mother?
Mother! Mother! Mother!
Let my son go, Flatyos.
Your son will die, Lena.
He shouldn't have entered this castle.
Flatyos. Let my son go.
Take me as a captive.
Taking you?
Lena, there are only two
things that I want.
The first is taking revenge
from my father's murderer.
The second is seeing you as
my wife, Lena.
In return for your son's life...
...I want you to...
...live here, in this castle
with me.
Your son will return to his tribe.
Stay with me here.
I'm hearing right, Flatyos.
Am I not?
You want me to release Savcı's son.
Is that so?
Wouldn't you do this for me, Nikola?
We'll release him and ambush him.
Won't you do this for
your friend's love?
The woman came all this way
to the castle, Flatyos.
Be a man.
What do you know about love, Nikola?
Sir, Dündar Bey is here.
This is good news.
Good news.
Father.
My ghazi father.
My bey father.
Who knows what
you've been through?
How tough decisions
you had to take?
Your beloved ones and
your people.
Your family and your tribe.
Your lands...
...and your heart.
Your blood and your cause.
This position is the place
of decisions.
And it requires sacrifice.
The people come before
your beloved ones.
Your tribe is your family.
Without lands,
there are no hearts.
And our blood runs for
our cause.
But I won't leave anyone.
Neither my sword...
...nor my brothers,
nor...
...my nephew.
Dündar Bey, I'm tired of Osman.
You should become the bey
as soon as possible.
With the name of Allah.
The Kayıs have a bey, Nikola.
-And it's not easy to defeat him.
-That's why we are together, Dündar Bey.
To help each other.
So, your nephew Osman,
will he leave Kulucahisar?
You know that he will, Nikola.
-Where is Bayhoca?
-Flatyos, have them prepare Bayhoca.
See, that was what you wanted.
Dündar Bey.
You are a step closer
to the throne.
Because of me.
Don't forget that.
Thank you. Thank you.
Don't doubt that.
I beg you in Virgin Mary's name.
Save my son.
Take me.
Nikola accepted to release your
son, Lena.
We'll pray for a new life now.
-A new life.
-Yes, Lena.
When will my son leave
the castle?
He is about to leave, Lena.
Trust me.
What are you doing?
What are you doing, Lena?
Were you going to save your son...
...and kill yourself? Were you going to
save your son and kill yourself, Lena?
I told you before. Savcı is my
first and last love.
He will remain that until my
last breath.
Release my son and
take my life.
That's all I can give.
Osman accepted to give Kulucahisar
Castle for your son, Lena.
Dündar Bey came to get your son.
Thank God!
Thank God for this!
-Thank God!
-Soldiers!
Take her. We'll reunite her
with her son.
Thank God!
Brother, will we give
that castle now?
Tell me, Dumrul.
What should we do?
Should we defy Osman Bey's orders?
We lost many men
for that castle.
I joined Osman Bey to conquer
castles, not give them.
I know, Gencebey. I know.
I can't accept it either.
Traditions on one side,
Osman Bey's order on the other.
I'm helpless too, brother.
Cerkutay, what are you doing there?
Bamsı Bey taught me that alps
don't ask questions.
So, I'm doing archery training.
Aygül Hatun, don't you have
a thing to say?
For me, Osman Bey is
the laws and the bey.
This sword is under his command.
If he says, swing,
I swing. If not, I'll forget it.
Not only Kulucahisar, even if
he gives Söğüt with it...
...I won't say a word.
-Salam Alaikum.
-Alaikum Salam.
-Any wounded?
-No, my bey.
My bey, Nikola accepted it.
They'll give Bayhoca.
-Thank Allah.
Thank Allah.
My bey, will we really give
the castle?
Mother, tell me. How do you know
Flatyos?
Thank God, we left that castle.
There is no need to think that.
Mother, how do you know Flatyos?
Turks are leaving the castle.
-What about the christians?
-None are left, sir.
Good news.
Alexander, search the castle.
Dündar Bey's companion will
come with you.
No living creature will be left
in the castle.
Kill everything that moves.
I'll wait for your news.
-Are you afraid that Osman might act up?
-I'm taking measures.
Otherwise, I will burn them alive.
You will die as well, Dündar Bey.
I know. I know.
-I know.
-Pray that...
...your nephew won't make a mistake.
The castle is empty. Here is our flag.
Now, Dündar Bey will bring Bayhoca
and Lena Hatun.
If anything goes wrong...
...slit their throats.
Search everywhere!
Check the secret passage!
Sir, it's empty.
Sir, the secret passage is empty.
Has Osman Bey kept his word?
Easy victories scare me.
We searched everywhere. There was
no one but two drunkards. We killed them.
Go and tell Flatyos that the castle
is ours.
-And give him the escrow.
-Yes, commander.
Long live Nikola!
Long live Alexander!
Get to the walls!
The castle is secure.
Long live Nikola!
Long live Alexander!
The castle is clear, sir.
Dündar Bey.
Thanks to them, we are having
a bloodless victory.
And by the way, it's that easy
to defeat Osman Bey.
Now, I'm the ruler of here.
It's the oath of the lord of Kulucahisar
Alexander.
Karacahisar and Söğüt are next in line.
I will end the Kayı!
Long live Nikola!
Long live Alexander!
Don't, son. Don't.
Who has more reason to cry, mother?
Because of me, Osman Bey
left Kulucahisar Castle.
How can I look at Osman Bey?
How can I look at the people, uncle?
We left the castle that was taken
with blood, because of me!
This shame is ours together, Bayhoca.
The ones who caused this should
be ashamed.
In time, everything will be done.
I thought Osman Bey had an iron will,
Dündar Bey.
But he is softhearted enough to
give us a castle for this idiot.
Bayhoca! Bayhoca!
Get out of here before I change my
mind and hang you.
Come on. Come on, let's go.
Mother, I can't live with this shame.
Come on, son. Let's go.
Osman gave the castle but he'll
do everything to take it back.
With the supply we brought, we can
defend it for months.
Osman doesn't have a single spy.
He can't enter the castle.
-He has to siege Kulucahisar.
-Isn't this what we want?
He should so that we can crush the
Turks inside and out with Nikola.
-What are you doing here, woman?
-I'm hanging clothes, don't you see?
Dresses of my children,
my stupid husband's clothes...
A woman's job never ends.
Don't you have anything to do?
We missed you. We missed you,
Abdurrahman Ghazi. We missed you.
You disappeared suddenly.
But you did a great job.
-So, alps are ready for a mission, huh?
-We missed you too.
That's what Osman Bey ordered.
He wanted me to...
...form a death squad which will
hunt...
...Geyhatu's commanders.
Thank Allah, that's what we did.
Mashallah. Mashallah.
Arslan Bey, Osman Bey invites you
to Kulucahisar.
He invites you to his jihad.
It's a must for a Muslim to accept
an invite for jihad.
Of course, we will come.
But tell me, Bamsı Bey...
...did you believe that Osman Bey
would give the castle?
Good question, Arslan Bey.
Back in time...
...when Ertuğrul Ghazi did things that
we couldn't understand, we believed in him.
Now we do the same for
Osman Bey.
Attack, my valiants!
-Ya Allah!
-For Allah!
It's not enough to put soldiers
on the walls.
We also need hot oil.
On north--
-Turks are in the castle, they are attacking!
-God damn it! How could that happen?
Osman!
Alps! In our tradition...
...can we leave a conquered castle?
-No, my bey.
-Can a bey step over the traditions?
-That's what I'm saying.
A conquered castle can never be
given back.
-The traditions can't be stepped over.
-Won't we save Bayhoca, my bey?
We'll save Bayhoca.
And Kulucahisar will be their
graveyard.
Come on! What are you waiting for?
-It's time for jihad.
-All right, my bey.
Catch them!
Ayaz, Gencebay!
-Swing your swords for Allah!
-Attack, my lions! Allahu Akbar!
Allahu Akbar!
I will kill you this time, Osman.
I swear that I will.
I will give you my life,
as I gave you the castle.
Come and keep your oath.
What are you doing here, mad girl?
I'm doing what you are doing,
mad lad. I'm fighting for the Kayı.
You may get hurt.
-Mind your business!
-This is my business!
Osman Bey is in the castle.
Hurry!
-May Allah bless your hands.
-Stop talking and run to the castle.
Lead the way.
Now.
Keep your oath.
This is your last chance...
...to kill me.
Your corpse will leave my castle, Osman.
I will raid your tribe and
kill everyone.
-Osman Bey!
Before dying...
...I want you to know.
Ask for their saddles from Turks,
and they will.
Ask for their horses,
When you are in tough times,
they will give you their bread.
When they are trapped,
they will give their lives.
But...
...even a crumble of soil that
was washed with blood...
...can never be given
without a fight.
When weasels set a trap,
wolves bleed.
But when wolves set a trap,
all weasels die.
Now, I have my nephew...
...and the castle.
Osman Bey, now we have the castle.
Thank you.
Dündar Bey took Lena and
Bayhoca to the tribe.
My bey, let's reach to the tribe
before Bayhoca runs out of tears.
Now, he is ready to be an alp.
Boran, send Alexander...
...to his owner's door.
We should send a gift back.
As you order, my bey.
Osman Bey leaves Kulucahisar for
his nephew. May Allah help us.
What's wrong, Aksu Hatun?
What are you doing here?
-I came to save you from your thoughts.
-What thought?
I heard that our bey is a captive.
True. Kayı beys are thinking for a
way to save him.
You came for nothing.
Forgive me for acting over my level.
If you allow me.
My daughter, come. Sit.
Tell us how to be saved from
our thoughts.
May Allah bless us.
I saw a dream last night.
I hope it's good.
There was a baby. Crying
in flames.
A woman was crying to save
that baby.
Then, a wolf showed up,
jumped into the flames.
The baby mounted the wolf, got out
of the flames and reunited with his mother.
The baby is Bayhoca.
He will reunite with his mother.
-Inshallah.
-I will return to Söğüt.
If you need something, tell me.
Stay here, Aksu Hatun.
I need you.
I've been waiting for this
for a long time.
Interesting enough, it was easy.
Let's take over our castle.
Yes.
Helen?
Dear Helen,
without losing a single soldier...
...a single soldier,
we took that castle!
-Nikola.
-Why did you dress like this?
Why do you look like a crow
in our victory day?
Nikola.
Helen?
Is something wrong?
-Osman...
-So, Helen? Osman?
Soldiers!
What's in the box, Helen?
Alexander...
My friend...
Osman...
Osman!
Burn it.
Ashes to ashes...
... dust to dust.
Your God has already left us, Petrus.
May God forgive your sins.
The God?
I never worshipped your God
for my empire.
But I might worship the devil
from now, Petrus.
You will tell me everything now!
First, what do you want from Osman?
Second, what do you want to
take from him?
No games, no lies.
You will tell me everything.
Tell me before sending you to devil.
Since you understood that the path
to God goes from the devil...
...you deserve to learn the truth,
Nikola.
The future of the Turks...
...is in Osman's tent.
To stop the Turks...
...to take their future from them...
...it's time for that great war.
-What does that mean?
-To unite the tribes...
...Osman has that great power.
And if does that,
it will be your doom first...
...then it will be our doom, Nikola.
When Kayı Tribe is in chaos,
we'll enter Osman's tent...
...and get the documents.
Bamsı will open the door...
...for his tent.
İdris Bey, İdris Bey!
Why are you chasing me?
What medicine is this?
It's healing, Bamsı Bey. I've been
searching for this since I saw your hand.
Sit, sit. Will this help me?
Yes, will you die if
you try it?
If it heals, you will fight
with two swords as you used to before.
Give it to me.
-Will I put it in my hand?
-Yes, on your hand.
Like this.
-What's this, sir?
-You'll give it to Bamsı.
It will heal his hand.
It will be so good that he will
ask for more.
As he wants more,
we'll give him more.
We should spread it like this so
it can heal you.
We'll see, İdris Bey.
We'll see.
Move!
Sargun Bey!
Merciless leader of the Cumans!
I brought you Lord Nikola's regards!
I brought you gold.
A lot of gold for the most
merciless warriors I've ever seen.
I came to give gold to those who
came for it.
I came to rain gold on you.
Sargun Bey!
This is the beginning!
Targun Hatun!
-Göktuğ?
-I came to end our deal, Flatyos.
Göktuğ and I killed Sargun...
...who took my father's throne.
From now, I'm leading the Cumans.
So, you came to take revenge,
Targun Hatun?
Yes, for revenge.
In a most bloody way. In most
cruel way.
The gold we'll get from Nikola...
...the spoils we'll get from Turkish
lands...
...but most importantly,
the revenge we'll get from Osman.
-Are you following me?
-You don't know where to go.
Just because Osman Bey sent me
away, I'm not homeless.
-I know where to go.
-You are right. You have a tribe to go.
I left the Mongols for Osman Bey.
Now I have nowhere to go.
What will you do now?
I'll make living by my sword.
Someone will need me.
I came for a new agreement.
But, don't forget.
I haven't forgotten anything yet.
Dodurğa, Bayat, Salur Tribes...
...they are spread everywhere.
Mongols left no unity.
We need to unite them,
for a new cause.
For new goals,
we need to unite them.
These escrows,
my ancestors...
...shout ''Are you still
waiting, Osman?''
They ask where our state is.
All tribes will come together.
I'll give them a home.
I'll give them lands,
goals.
I'll build an army.
And I will kick the heathens
out of these lands.
I promised you, father.
I will keep my word.
Oh, my son. Oh...
Bayhoca, when your father comes,
whatever he says...
...don't say a thing.
-Do you get it?
-He will come at you because of me.
How can you do this?
How?
Father, I made a mistake but--
Bayhoca...
But?
But people died because of you!
-People!
-Savcı Bey!
You destroyed my honor!
How can you go to that castle
without telling me?
How?
Also...
...with a child on your belly...
Hit me, Savcı Bey.
Go on.
Hit to a mother who is
in pain for her child.
My Allah, you are the one who
gives patience to us.
Woman, we live for our honor,
don't you know that?
We'll die if needed.
But...
Are you ashamed? Huh?
Tell me, are you ashamed?
Your mother begged to the enemy!
Are you ashamed?
I am ashamed, father.
I'm ashamed for causing all this.
Be ashamed.
You too.
From now, if you do anything
without telling me...
...I will kill you both with
my own hands.
-Father?
-Savcı!
-Father!
-Father, are you all right?
-Savcı, are you all right?
I'm fine.
He came and ruined everything.
He played us all by saying
he will give the castle.
While we were talking about
it in the tent...
...he set his game already.
Woman, leave that and say something.
I'm waiting for you to calm down,
Dündar Bey.
Last time, when you were
choking me...
...you said something.
What did you say?
Don't push an angry man!
Was that what you said?
Yeah, I said.
But I didn't tell you to not
speak a word.
Do you know why Osman
succeeds...
...and you do not?
Yes, tell me. Tell me.
When Osman builds a plan,
he trusts in himself.
But you trust in others.
Should I be silent or leave?
What should I do? Huh?
What should I do?
Build your own plan...
...and don't trust anyone.
You are right.
In Bayhoca Matter...
...we are guilty...
...after all, we kept him away
from the tribe.
We wanted him to
know science...
...learn trade.
These are surely important.
But for a Kayı bey...
...responsibility is the most important.
A Kayı bey should know...
...that the price is heavy,
when he makes a mistake.
You can't learn it from a school,
but from experience.
You are right, brother.
But...
...we sent them to not
suffer as we did...
...to get good education.
I know, brother. I know.
That's what I'm saying.
Our children shouldn't go away.
Science shouldn't
be away from us.
It should be here.
Teachers should come here.
Firstly, we should be students.
Then, we should teach.
Inshallah, brother.
I don't know if we'll see those days.
-But inshallah, they will.
-Inshallah.
They will, brother. They will.
I wish we could too.
But, a three doesn't grow in one day.
And you, Bayhoca...
...you owe me now.
You won't act on your own.
When I say jihad,
you'll go to jihad.
When I say sit,
you'll sit.
If you don't listen to me,
if you make your parents sad again...
...then, you'll see my fury.
I got my lesson, Osman Bey.
From now, I will listen to my mother...
...to my father
and to you.
May I enter, my bey?
Come.
-My bey, Kumrul Abdal wants to come.
-Let him come.
Why are you sitting like this?
-Someone is coming, Osman Bey!
-Who is that?
One who solves all mysteries...
...one who has a throne in our hearts,
sultan of Ahis, Sheikh Edebali!
Father!
My Sheikh, Edebali.
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com